Transcription by CastingWords
CastingWords
The Eurasian continent was attacked by a massive spatial quake.
There were 150 million victims of this unprecedented event.
And now...
Sounded sung
Blood
Clean
Make up
Don't
свобод
podcast
Follow
Where
you
In the world, I don't know what to do
I'm still afraid of the beauty
I'm still afraid of the heart
I'm still afraid of you
Wake up!
My little sister is giving me what could possibly be the worst wake-up call ever
Godry, darling little sister of mine
What is it, darling big brother of mine?
Get off of me! You're too big!
Sorry, did that hurt? I bet you're awake though
Hey! Don't just go right back to sleep!
Wake up! Come on, wake up sleepyhead, wake up!
Listen to me, run away
Huh?
I've contracted the mysterious ten more minutes of sleep
Or else my sister goes to tickle hell virus
Often referred to as the T-virus for short
What? You've got what?
Run away, Kotry
Run!
Or I can still control myself
Wait! But then what's gonna happen to you, bro?
As long as you're safe
It doesn't matter what happens to me
Run away
No, I can't! I can't leave you!
Нач
Okay, much better
Much better.
Huh?
I don't want to go to Tickle Hell!
Someone help me!
It's me! Calm down, it's only me.
Are you sure?
I am much good friend to you. Yes, my coterie big brother.
A spatial quake was recorded early this morning near the center of Tengu City.
There was only slight damage, with no casualties among residents in the area.
Investigations continue as to the cause of the spatial quakes.
Again?
Sounded close, too.
It was.
Spatial quakes. Widespread vibration phenomena.
An area randomly starts vibrating and no one knows why.
These quakes are irrational, mysterious, and unbelievably destructive.
After the massive catastrophe 30 years ago, spatial quakes continued around the world for six terrifying months.
In Japan, the great southern Kanto spatial quake completely flattened an area not too far from our house.
It was total devastation.
In the 25 years after that, nothing happened. Nothing.
Until five years ago, when a spatial quake showed up in the redeveloped Tengu City.
Not long after that, we started hearing about quakes all the time.
Most of which occurred here in Japan.
It's weird. There have been a lot lately.
You're telling me this is happening earlier than planned.
Hold it! No sweets!
No sweets!
Seriously?
Just make sure you eat breakfast, okay?
Okay, bro. I love you.
Oh, hey. You got any requests for lunch?
Oh, yeah! One deluxe kid's plate!
That's from a diner menu.
We don't serve that dish at this restaurant.
Ah! Come on. Oh, please. Pretty please.
Put the cherry on top.
It's yummy.
Ow.
Deluxe kid's plate wins!
I love eating out for lunch.
It's a diner. Not that exciting.
Uh-huh. Thank you so much, bro.
Okay, so after school, I'll be waiting for you right here in front of the restaurant.
Sounds good.
And don't break your promise. Be here no matter what happens.
Even if the place is taken over by terrorists, we'll still eat!
If that goes down, I doubt they'll let us stay.
I'll be here.
Be careful on your way to school.
Hey, isn't that Cheeto eats guy?
Do they seem too close?
Cause I've heard he's got a weird sister complex.
That's so lame.
Don't forget you promised me, so I'm gonna be here ready to eat even if a spatial quake happens.
Sweet. Now go to school already.
Well, hey there. What's up?
Hey, Tonomachi.
You ready for the semester? You sure look like you are.
Oh, have you also heard the rumors about him?
Yeah, he swings both ways, as they say.
That's so lame.
Are you okay, Ai?
I'm perfect. I just saw a super genius creepin'.
That's so lame.
Nice coincidence, huh, Cheeto?
Lucky you being put in the same class with me again.
Some people would call this fate.
I would be one of those people.
Of course you would.
Hold on.
Excuse me.
It's my girl.
What?
A girl like girlfriend?
Oh yeah, you wanna meet her?
Check it out.
That's a dating sim.
Yeah, so what?
Doesn't change the fact that she's my girlfriend.
Don't judge me. A dating sim will tell you everything you need to know about how to treat women.
It's like a textbook for lovin'.
This particular app is groovy because she lives on the floor.
Who?
Me?
Yes.
How do you know my name?
You mean you don't remember?
Hmm.
Oh yeah, you wanna meet her?
Check it out.
That's a dating sim.
Yeah, so what?
Doesn't change the fact that she's my girlfriend.
Don't judge me.
A dating sim will tell you everything you need to know about how to treat women.
It's like a textbook for lovin'.
This particular app is groovy because she lives on the floor.
Shito Itsuka.
Who?
Me?
Yes.
How do you know my name?
You mean you don't remember?
Hmm.
Hey, who is she?
Am I supposed to know her?
Of course you are.
That is Origami Tobiichi, otherwise known as the super genius.
For real?
Crazy.
She knows me?
That chick always has some of the best grades in our class.
She's ridiculous at sports and I mean look at her.
Gorgeous.
On my girls I probably ought to have as a girlfriend list, she's never been out of the top three.
Like, ever.
How do you not know one of the most popular kids in our school?
But more importantly, why in the world does Origami know who you are?
I wish I knew, but I have no idea.
Oh, heck yeah!
It's Tamae.
It's Miss Okamine, please.
Now quiet down.
I'll be your homeroom teacher this year.
I hope you guys are ready to learn.
Origami Tobiichi.
Why does she know who I am?
And why is she looking at me?
So weird.
What the heck is going on?
Hey, Shido.
Want to go home together?
Sorry, I don't got plans.
Oh yeah?
Is it a girl?
Technically.
It's just coterie though.
Oh, I understand.
Besides, as far as I know, there's not a girl in the world.
I don't know.
Hey, Shido.
Want to go home together?
Sorry.
I don't got plans.
Oh yeah?
Is it a girl?
Technically.
It's just coterie though.
Oh, I understand.
Besides, as far as I know, there's not a girl in this school with a sensitive and kind
enough spirit to have lunch with you.
Thanks, but that was not a compliment.
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill.
There's not a drill.
A spatial quake.
Another one?
We need to evacuate.
The shelter near the school should be safe enough.
I repeat.
There have been precursory signs that have been a spatial quake.
Where's she going?
Contriella.
Aura Abu Yurotime's Club.
Intensive terror photo.
Shigelsa Tariq on my fence.
Monsto Machinihi Princess.
Ah, she's here.
I repeat.
There have been precursory signs that have been an impending spatial quake as a vicinity.
Please evacuate to the air of shelter immediately.
This is not a drill.
I repeat.
There have been precursory signs that have been an impending spatial quake as a vicinity.
Please evacuate to the air of shelter immediately.
Let me see.
It's not a drill.
Everyone, please calm down.
And don't bring in your 3Ds.
Don't push.
Don't run.
Don't walk.
Wait.
You might want to take it down, Skosh.
Of course.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Surely she's not still gonna try to meet me at the diner.
I'll be here even if a spatial quake happens.
Come on.
Please don't be waiting in front of that diner.
She has to have gone to a shelter.
She's fine.
She's gotta be fine.
I bet the shelter she's in just has bad reception.
Or she has her phone on silent or something.
Let me check her location.
Just in case.
No!
Hey!
Wait!
Shito!
Okay, bro.
I love you!
Why?
Thank you so much, bro!
Why does she not just take shelter?
The city's about to be destroyed and she's worried about a promise?
Kotori, Kotori, Kotori, Kotori!
Whoa, what was that?
It's... a girl.
What's she doing?
Not you, too.
I see... so it's true.
You came here to kill me.
Do not try denying you are here to kill me.
I must deal with you before the others arrive.
Wait!
Just wait, please!
That's...
That's not why I came here.
What?
I...
I could never kill anybody.
Is that what you're here for?
Why do they not realize the futility of their attacks?
This isn't just any girl.
If she's that strong, why does she look so sad?
heal my leg?
Yeah!
Tobechi? Is that you?
Shida, it's you.
Why are you wearing those clothes?
No!
Coordinates FJ1820. The target, Princess, has been lost.
Area reaction waves below detection threshold.
Hello?
That is confirmed. Finally, we meet again.
Who are you?
I'm so glad that just we had. Just a little while longer. I won't ever let you go again. I won't ever be wrong again. Soon.
Hmm. It appears you're awake now.
Wait. I don't know you. Who are you?
My name is Reina Murasame. Just call me Reina. I'm the head analyst here. There's no reason for you to freak out. First aid is hardly out of my league.
That's supposed to be reassuring. So, here's a question. Where exactly am I?
You're resting in Fraxinus' sickbay. You are unconscious, so it was decided this was the best course of action.
Fraxinus' what now? Did I pass out? Oh, right. I ended up in the middle of that chick fight.
Wait. Coterie. But my sister. I need to go find my sister. She's waiting for me in front of the diner. She could be...
What you need is to calm down. Your sister is perfectly fine.
What? She is?
I'm assuming you want some sort of explanation now? Apologies, but that isn't really my forte. You should ask the vice commander for more details.
I've brought him with me.
Thank you for taking care of him. It's very nice to meet you. My name is Kyohei Kanazuki, and I am the vice commander. Welcome, Shido. We're glad you're here.
Coterie?
Glad you could make it, bro. Like the idiot said, welcome to Rattata-skirt.
Penetration angle, check. Anus, set.
Police. Connection.
I got you. Good work.
Captain Kasabe.
You're working yourself too hard. Take it easy, okay?
This thing is a monster called a spirit. It was lost not long ago. That means it disappeared. And this is what we call it...
Wait, will you shut up for a second?
Don't be rude. The commander's taking the time to explain everything to you personally. You should be on your knees bowing in gratitude.
If you want, I certainly wouldn't mind letting you lick my boots while you're down there.
What? Really? I can?
Oh, yeah. Thank you for that, commander.
And, uh, you are Coterie.
Of course. Have you forgotten what my face looks like? Shido.
No, bro.
I knew your memory was bad, but not Alzheimer's bad.
Well, I guess we'll have to admit you to a nursing home pretty soon.
So, uh, what's going on? Where are we?
Quit freaking. I'll explain the specifics to you later, but first, you need to remember the three things I'm about to say.
One, that girl is a spirit. She doesn't belong in this world, and simply appearing on our planet causes everything around her to blow up whether she wants it to or not.
Blow up? Why?
You are so dumb. You know those things we call spatial quakes? Well, spirits just like that girl down there are the ones responsible for making them happen.
How could one girl do all that?
Ready for two?
These are the Ground Force's anti-spirits team. When a spirit appears, the AST fly to their location and take care of it. Meaning they kill them.
What? Kill them?
It's true. You came here to kill me, didn't you?
And now for three. There is another way to deal with these spirits without having to rely on the AST.
This is the reason you're here and where your help will be most needed.
Me? Help how?
We'll have to make sure you start training tomorrow. I'll leave the rest of the details up to the person in charge of your development. In the meantime, just go back to school like normal.
Wait, will you slow down? Why would you train me? I mean, seriously, what could I possibly do?
No one is asking your opinion on the matter. Your only option is yes.
Now I have a question. What were you doing down there, Cheeto? Did you want to die?
No, stupid. I was looking for you.
Remember, you said you'd be at the diner even if there was a quake.
I said that. But how was I supposed to know you'd follow through?
Look, Kotori. Besides being dependable, your phone's locator showed me you were there.
You don't say.
Oh yeah, I guess that does make sense.
Although, technically we're above the diner.
Huh?
Disable the filter.
We're currently 15,000 meters above Tengu City.
You're on board an airship called Fraxinus.
It's everything.
is everyone enjoying day two of the new semester well i am because today we have a brand new
assistant homeroom teacher with us i'm reina murosame and i'm excited to be here
how did you get to be one of my teachers tell me what's going on please miss murosame you can just
call me reina keishin my name is shido is that right wow sorry shin my bad you can't be serious
come on you didn't even try getting it right it's more convenient for me to keep close to you if
i'm a member of the school's teaching staff and you should have been able to figure that much out
on your own try not to be so stupid hey why don't you tell me why you're even here don't you have
school i got permission to come today fine so are you finally going to explain to me what this training
is for or what it'll start to make more sense once you start using the training software hit it reina
huh this is a dating sim todomachi was playing it um no it's not take another look
oh my little shido
oh
That thing is an enemy that I must defeat.
Why?
You really think they're so evil?
Spirits killed my parents.
They burned them.
They are very evil.
And they will pay.
Why?
You're so iso.
It's a long way